Guide to the Samuel Stark Film stills: photographs, 1925-1972
Department of Special Collections
- 358. "Girl Rush"1944 (Box 5)
  Frances Langford, Wally Brown
- 359. "Girls of Pleasure Island" (Box 5)
  Leo Genn, Don Taylor
- 360. "Glad Tidings" (Box 5)
  Barbara Kelly, Raymond Huntley
- 361. "The Glass Slipper" (Box 5)
  Leslie Caron, Michael Wilding
- 362. "The Glory Guys" (Box 5)
  Tom Tryon, Harve Presnell, Senta Berger
- 363. "The Gnome-Mobile" (Box 5)
  Walter Brennan, Tom Lowell, Ed Wynn
- 364. "Go Into Your Dance"1935 (Box 5)
  Al Jolson, Ruby Keeler
- 365. "Go West"1940 (Box 5)
  The Marx Brothers, Mae McGuire, Diana Lewis
- 366. "Gold Rush"1928 (Box 5)
  Charlie Chaplin, Mark Swain
- 367. "The Golden Mistress" (Box 5)
  John AGar, Rosemarie Bowe
- 368. "Goldfinger"1964 (Box 5)
  Sean Connery, Honor Blackman, Gert Frobe
- 369. "Gone With The Wind"1939 (Box 5)
  Clark Gable, Vivien Leigh
- 370. "The Good Earth"1936 (Box 5)
  Paul Muni, Luise Rainer
- 371. "The Goose Girl" (Box 5)
  Marguerite Clark
- 372. "The Gorgeous Hussy" (Box 5)
  Joan Crawford, Sidney Toler
- 373. "Grand Hotel"1932 (Box 5)
  Lewis Stone, Lionel Barrymore
- 374. "A Great Citizen" (Box 5)
  Z. Fedorova
- 375. "The Great Escape"1963 (Box 5)
  Steve McQueen, James Garner, Richard Attenborough, James Donald, Donald Pleasance
- 376. "The Great Geatsby" (Box 5)
  Alan Ladd, Betty Field, MacDonald Carey
- 377. "The Great Man" (Box 5)
  Jose Ferrer, Dean Jagger, Keenan Wynn
- 378. "The Great Missouri Raid" (Box 5)
  MacDonald Carey, Wendell Corey
- 379. "The Great Profile" (Box 5)
- 380. "The Great St. Trinian's Train Robbery" (Box 5)
  Frankie Howerd, Dora Bryan
- 381. "The Great Victor Herbert"1939 (Box 5)
  Allan Jones, Mary Martin
- 382. "The Great Waltz" (Box 5)
  Luise Rainer, Fernand Gravet
- 383. "The Great Ziegfeld"1936 (Box 5)
  A. A. Trimble, William Powell, Myrna Loy, Luise Rainer
- 384. "The Greatest Show on Earth" (Box 5)
- 385. "Greed" (Box 5)
  Gilbert Gowland, Zazu Pitts
- 386. "The Green Scarf" (Box 5)
  Michael Redgrave, Leo Genn
- 387. "The Guardsman"1931 (Box 5)
  Alfred Lunt, Joan Fontanne
- 388. "A Guide for the Married Man" (Box 5)
  Walter Matthau, Robert Morse, Inger Stevens, Sue Ann Langdon
- 389. "This Gun For Hire" (Box 5)
  Alan Ladd, Veronica Lake
- 390. "Gun Fury" (Box 5)
  Rock Hudson, Donna Reed
- 391. "The Gun Runners" (Box 5)
  Audie Murphy, Eddie Albert
- 392. "Guys and Dolls" (Box 5)
  Frank Sinatra, Marlon Brando, Jean Simmons, Vivian Blaine
- 393. "H.M.S. Defiant" (Box 5)
  Alec Guinness, Dirk Bogarde
- 394. "Hamlet"1953 (Box 5)
  Laurence Olivier
- 395. "Hammerhead"1968 (Box 5)
  Vince Edwards, Judy Geeson
- 396. "The Hanging Tree" (Box 5)
  Gary Cooper, Maria Schell, Karl Malden
- 397. "Hansel and Gretel" (Box 5)
- 398. "The Happening" (Box 5)
  Martha Hyer, Oscar Homolka
- 399. "Happy Anniversary" (Box 5)
  David Niven, Mitzi Gaynor
- 400. "A Hard Day's Night"1964 (Box 5)
  The Beatles, Wilfrid Brambell
- 401. "Harry and Tonto"1974 (Box 5)
  Art Carney
- 402. "Harry Black" (Box 5)
  Stewart Granger, Barbara Rush
- 403. "Has Anyone Seen My Gal" (Box 5)
  Piper Laurie, Charles Coburn, Rock Hudson
- 404. "He Learned About Women"1932 (Box 5)
  Stuart Erwin, Alison Skipworth
- 405. "The Heart of a Follies Girl"1928 (Box 5)
  Mildren Harris, Billie Dane
- 406. "Heart of a Man" (Box 5)
  Frankie Vaughan, Anne Heywood
- 407. "Hearts Divided"1936 (Box 5)
  Dick Powell
- 408. "Hearts of the World"1926 (Box 6)
  Dorothy Gish, Lillian Gish
- 409. "Heidi and Peter" (Box 6)
- 410. "Hell to Eternity" (Box 6)
  Jeffrey Hunter, Vic Damone
- 411. "Henry V"1958 (Box 6)
- 412. "Here Comes Cookie"1935 (Box 6)
  George Burns, Gracie Allen
- 413. "Hidden Fear" (Box 6)
  John Payne, Alexander Knox, Conrad Nagel
- 414. "The High Bright Sun" (Box 6)
  Dirk Bogarde, George Chakris
- 415. "High Jump" (Box 6)
  Richard Wyler, Lisa Daniely
- 416. "High, Wide, and Handsome"1937 (Box 6)
  Irene Dunne, Randolph Scott, Dorothy Lamour
- 417. "His First Command" (Box 6)
  William Boyd, Dorothy Sebastian
- 418. "Hid Kind of Woman" (Box 6)
  Robert Mitchum, Jane Russell
- 419. "The History of Mr. Polly" (Box 6)
  John Mills, Sally Ann Howes
- 420. "Hitler's Children" (Box 6)
- 421. "Hold Back Tomorrow" (Box 6)
  Cleo Moore, John Agar
- 422. "Hold Everything" (Box 6)
  Joe Brown
- 423. "Holiday Affair" (Box 6)
  Janet Leigh, Wendell Corey, Robert Mitchum
- 424. "The Holly and the Ivy" (Box 6)
  Ralph Richardson, Celia Johnson
- 425. "Hollywood Hotel" (Box 6)
  Rosemary and Lola Lane, Hugh Herbert
- 426. "Hollywood Revue of 1929" (Box 6)
  Oliver Hardy, Stan Laurel, Jack Benny
- 427. "Hombre" (Box 6)
  Paul Newman, Fredric March, Richard Boone
- 428. "Honeymoon Hotel" (Box 6)
  Robert Goulet, Nancy Kwan
- 429. "Honky Tonk" (Box 6)
  George Bancroft
- 430. "Honor Among Lovers"1931 (Box 6)
  Claudette Colbert, Fredric March
- 431. "Hot Enough For June" (Box 6)
  Dirk Bogarde, Sylva Koscina
- 432. "The House of Rothschild" (Box 6)
  George Arliss, Loretta Young,
- 433. "How To Murder Your Wife" (Box 6)
  Jack Lemmon, Virna Lisi
- 434. "The Hummingbird"1924 (Box 6)
  Gloria Swanson
- 435. "The Hunchback of Notre Dame" (Box 6)
  Gina Lollobrigida, Anthony Quinn
- 436. "I Live My Life"1935 (Box 6)
  Joan Crawford, Brian Aherne
- 437. "I Married a Communist" (Box 6)
  Lorraine Day, Robert Ryan, Thomas Gomez
- 438. "I Married A Woman"1956 (Box 6)
  George Gobel, Diana Dors, Adolphe Menjou
- 439. "I Remember Mama"1948 (Box 6)
- 440. "I Saw What You Did" (Box 6)
  Joan Crawford, John Ireland
- 441. "I Take This Woman"1931 (Box 6)
  Gary Cooper, Carole Lombard
- 442. "I Want You" (Box 6)
  Dana Andrews, Dorothy McGuire
- 443. "I Was Happy Here" (Box 6)
  Julian Glover, Sarah Miles
- 444. "I Was Monty's Double" (Box 6)
  John Mills, Cecil Parker
- 445. "If I Were King"1938 (Box 6)
  Ronald Colman, Frances Dee, Basil Rathbone
- 446. "If You Knew Susie"1947 (Box 6)
  Joan Davis, Eddie Cantor
- 447. "I'm All Right Jack" (Box 6)
  Ian Carmichael, Terry-Thomas
- 448. "The Impatient Maiden"1931 (Box 6)
  Mae Clarke, Lew Ayres
- 449. "In Caliente" (Box 6)
- 450. "In Cold Blood" (Box 6)
  Robert Blake, Scott Wilson, John Forsythe
- 451. "In Like Flint" (Box 6)
  James Coburn, Lee J. Cobb, Jean Hale
- 452. "Indiscreet" (Box 6)
  Gloria Swanson, Ben Lyon
- 453. "Inez From Hollywood" (Box 6)
  Anna Q. Nilson, Lewis Stone
- 454. "The Informers" (Box 6)
  Michael Coles, Nigel Patrick
- 455. "The Intelligence Men" (Box 6)
  Ernie Wise, Eric Morecambe
- 456. "The Interns"1963 (Box 6)
- 457. "Intruder in the Dust" (Box 6)
  David Brian, Claude Jarman, Jr.
- 458. "The Invisible Man" (Box 6)
- 459. "The Invisible Ray"1935 (Box 6)
- 460. "Is Paris Burning?" (Box 6)
  Jean-Paul Belmondo, Charles Boyer, Leslie Caron
- 461. "Island Escape" (Box 6)
  Jeffrey Hunter, Marshall Thompson
- 462. "It's A Boy"1942 (Box 6)
  Leslie Henson, Edward Everett Horton
- 463. "It's A Grand Life" (Box 6)
  Frank Randle, Diana Dors
- 464. "It's All Happening" (Box 6)
  Tommy Steele, Angela Douglas
- 465. "Jack the Giant Killer" (Box 6)
  Kerwin Matthews, Judi Meredith
- 466. "Jane Eyre" (Box 6)
  Joan Fantaine, Orson Welles, Margaret O'Brien
- 467. "Jealousy" (Box 6)
  John Loder, Jane Randolph
- 468. "Jesse James"1938 (Box 6)
  Tyrone Power, Nancy Kelly, Henry Fonda
- 469. "Joan of Ozark" (Box 6)
  Joe E. Brown, Judy Canova
- 470. "Joe Palooka Meets Humphrey" (Box 6)
  Leon Errol, Joe Kirkwood
- 471. "John Goldfarb, Please Come Home" (Box 6)
  Shirley MacLaine, Peter Ustinov, Richard Crenna
- 472. "John Paul Jones" (Box 6)
  Robert Stack, Thomas Gomez
- 473. "Johnny Apollo" (Box 6)
  Tyrone Power, Dorothy Lamour
- 474. "A Jolly Bad Fellow" (Box 6)
  Leo McKern, Janet Munro, Dennis Price
- 475. "Journey's End" (Box 6)
  David Warmers, Colin Clive, Ian Maclaren
- 476. "Juarez" (Box 6)
  Paul Muni, Bette Davis, John Garfield
- 477. "Jules Verne's Rocket to the Moon" (Box 6)
  Burl Ives, Troy Donohue
- 478. "Just For Fun" (Box 6)
  Mark Wynter, Bobby Vee, Cherry Roland
- 479. "Just Squaw" (Box 6)
  Beatriz Michelena
- 480. "Just William's Luck" (Box 6)
  William Graham, Leslie Bradley
- 481. "Kathy O" (Box 6)
  Dan Duryea, Jan Sterling
- 482. "Kelly and Me" (Box 6)
  Van Johnson, Piper Laurie
- 483. "Kentucky"1938 (Box 6)
  Loretta Young, Richard Greene
- 484. "The Key" (Box 6)
  William Holden, Sophia Loren, Trevor Howard
- 485. "The Keys of the Kingdom" (Box 6)
  Gregory Peck, Vincent Price
- 486. "The Kid"1920 (Box 6)
  Charlie Chaplin, Jackie Coogan
- 487. "King Kong"1931 (Box 6)
  Fay Wray, Robert Armstrong
- 488. "The King of Kings" (Box 6)
- 489. "King of the Bullwhip", 2 (Box 7)
- 490. "King of the Khyber Rifles"1929 (Box 7)
- 491. "King Richard III" (Box 7)
  1946
- 492. "Kismet", 3 (Box 7)
  Otis Skinner, Joe E. Brown
- 493. "Kismet" (Box 7)
  Howard Keel, Dolores Gray, Ann Blyth
- 494. "The Knack...and How to Get It"1965 (Box 7)
  Donal Donnelly, Michael Crawford, Ray Brooks
- 495. "Laddie"1940 (Box 7)
  Martha O'Driscoll, Tim Holt
- 496. "Ladies of Leisure" (Box 7)
  Barbara Stanwyck, Ralph Graves
- 497. "Lady Godiva"1955, 2 (Box 7)
  Maureen O'Hara, George Nader
- 498. "A Lady of Chance"1929 (Box 7)
- 499. "Lady of the Night"1925, 2 (Box 7)
  Norma Shearer
- 500. "The Lady Takes A Flyer"1957 (Box 7)
  Lana Turner, Jeff Chandler, Chuck Conners
- 501. "Lady of the Tropics", 8 (Box 7)
  Robert Taylor, Hedy Lamarr
- 502. "Lake Placid Serenade" (Box 7)
  Vera Hruba Ralston, Eugene Pallette
- 503. "Lancelot and Guinevere" (Box 7)
  Biran Aherne, Cornel Wilde, Jean
- 504. "The Last Days of Pompeii" (Box 7)
  Preston Foster, Alan Hale,
- 505. "The Last of the Mohicans"1936 (Box 7)
  Randolph Scott, Binnie
- 506. "The Last Outpost", 2 (Box 7)
  Cary Grant, Claude Rains
- 507. "Law and Disorder" (Box 7)
  Michael Redgrave, Robert Morley
- 508. "Lawrence of Arabia"1963 (Box 7)
  Peter O'Toole, Omar Sharif, Alec
- 509. "The Leatherneck" (Box 7)
  William Boyd
- 510. "Left, Right, and Centre" (Box 7)
  Alastair Sim, Patricia Bredin
- 511. "Legion of the Lawless"1939 (Box 7)
  George O'Brien, Virginia Vale
- 512. "The Lemon Drop Kid" (Box 7)
  Bob Hope, Marilyn Maxwell
- 513. "Let 'Em Have It"1935, 2 (Box 7)
  Richard Arlen, Virginia Bruce
- 514. "Let's Get Married"1926 (Box 7)
  Richard Dix, Lois Wilson
- 515. "License to Kill" (Box 7)
- 516. "Life at the Top"1958 (Box 7)
  Laurence Harvey, Jean Simmons, Honor Blackman
- 517. "Life Begins At 40"1935 (Box 7)
  Will Rogers, Richard Cromwell
- 518. "Life for Ruth", 2 (Box 7)
  Michael Craig, Janet Munro
- 519. "The Life of Emile Zola" (Box 7)
  Paul Muni
- 520. "Life of a Lancer Spy" (Box 7)
  Delores del Rio, George Sanders
- 521. "Lights Out" (Box 7)
  Arthur Kennedy
- 522. "The Lion and the Mouse" (Box 7)
  May McAvoy, Lionel Barrymore
- 523. "The Lion in Winter"1968, 2 (Box 7)
- 524. "Little Caesar", 3 (Box 7)
- 525. "Little Fugitive" (Box 7)
  Richie Andrusco
- 526. "Little Men"1940, 10 (Box 7)
  Kay Francis, Ann Gillis, Jim Lydon
- 527. "The Little Minister", 2 (Box 7)
  Katharine Hepburn
- 528. "Little Miss Marker"1934 (Box 7)
  Shirley Temple, Adolphe Menjou
- 529. "Little Miss Rebellion"1920 (Box 7)
  Dorothy Gish
- 530. "Little Old New York", 2 (Box 7)
  Marion Davies
- 531. "Lives of a Bengal Lancer"1934, 2 (Box 7)
  Gary Cooper
- 532. "The Living Desert", 4 (Box 7)
  Walt Disney film
- 533. "Lonely Are The Brave" (Box 7)
  Kirk Douglas, Walter Matthau
- 534. "The Long Day's Dying", 2 (Box 7)
  David Hemmings, Tony Beckley
- 535. "The Long Denial" (Box 7)
  Maureen O'Hara, Gloria Grahame (name changed to "A Woman's Secret")
- 536. "The Long Duel", 5 (Box 7)
  Yul Brynner, Trevor Howard
- 537. "The Long Night" (Box 7)
  Henry Fonda, Barbara Bel Geddes
- 538. "Lord Jim"1977, 4 (Box 7)
  Peter O'Toole, James Mason
- 539. "Lord of the Flies", 2 (Box 7)
  Hugh Edwards, James Aubrey
- 540. "Lost Horizon" (Box 7)
  Jane Wyatt, John Howard
- 541. "The Lost Hours" (Box 7)
  Mark Stevens, Jean Kent
- 542. "Lost Treasure of the Amazon" (Box 7)
  Fernando Lamas, Rhonda Fleming, Brian Keith
- 543. "The Lost World" (Box 7)
  Michael Rennie, Jill St. John
- 544. "Louis Pasteur" (Box 7)
- 545. "Love Is News"1937, 2 (Box 7)
  Loretta Young, Tyrone Power
- 546. "Love On The Dole", 2 (Box 7)
  Deborah Kerr, Clifford Evans
- 547. "Love On The Run"1936, 3 (Box 7)
  Clark Gable, Joan Crawford
- 548. "Lovers At Midnight" (Box 7)
  Danny Robin
- 549. "Loving Couples" (Box 7)
  Harriet Andersson, Gunnel Lindblom
- 550. "Lucky Dog"1933 (Box 7)
  Chick Sale
- 551. "Mack Sennett Girls", 10 (Box 7)
  Phyllis Haver
- 552. "Madame du Barry"1934, 2 (Box 7)
  Delores del Rio
- 553. "Mme Sans Gene"1925, 3 (Box 7)
- 554. "Madame X", 2 (Box 7)
  Keir Dullea, Lana Turner
- 555. "Madeleine"1950, 2 (Box 7)
- 556. "Mademoiselle Fifi"1944, 5 (Box 7)
  Darren William, Simone Simon
- 557. "Maedchen in Uniform", 14 (Box 7)
- 558. "Magnificent Obsession", 4 (Box 7)
- 559. "The Magnificent Showman" (Box 7)
  John Wayne, Claudia Cardinale,
- 560. "The Magnificent Two", 9 (Box 7)
  Eric Morecambe, Ernie Wise
- 561. "Mail Order Bride" (Box 7)
  Keir Dullea, Buddy Ebsen (press
- 562. "Make Way For Tomorrow"1937, 5 (Box 7)
  Beulah Bondi
- 563. "Male and Female" (Box 7)
  Mildred Reardon, Gloria Swanson
- 564. "Man About Town"1939, 2 (Box 7)
  Jack Benny, Dorothy Lamour
- 565. "The Man From Colorado", 3 (Box 7)
  William Holden, Glenn Ford
- 566. "The Man I Married" (Box 7)
  Joan Bennett, Francis Lederer
- 567. "The Man in Possession"1937 (Box 7)
  Robert Taylor, Jean Harlow
- 568. "Man in the Vault" (Box 7)
  William Campbell, Karen Sharpe, Anita Ekberg
- 569. "Man of Conquest" (Box 7)
  Richard Dix, Gail Patrick, Joan Fontaine
- 570. "The Man and the Moment" (Box 8)
  Billie Dove
- 571. "Man of Two Worlds"1934 (Box 8)
  Francis Lederer, Elissa Landi
- 572. "Man on the Eiffel Tower"1950 (Box 8)
  Burgess Meredith, Charles Laughton
- 573. "The Man Who Came Back"1931 (Box 8)
  Charles Farrell, Janet Gaynor
- 574. "The Man Who Died Twice", 2 (Box 8)
  Rod Cameron, Vera Ralston
- 575. "The Man Who Never Was" (Box 8)
  Clifton Webbe, Gloria Grahame
- 576. "Man, Woman, and Wife" (Box 8)
  Norman Kerry
- 577. "The Manchurian Candidate" (Box 8)
  Frank Sinatra, Laurence Harvey, Janet Leigh
- 578. "Many A Slip" (Box 8)
  Joan Bennett, Lew Ayres
- 579. "Many Happy Returns"1934 (Box 8)
  Guy Lombardo and His Royal Canadians, Geprge Birms. Gracoe Allen
- 580. "The March of Todd-Ao" (Box 8)
- 581. "Marie Galante" (Box 8)
  Spencer Tracy, Ketti Gallian
- 582. "Maroc 7", 2 (Box 8)
  Gene Barry, Tracy Reed
- 583. "The Marriage Playground"1929 (Box 8)
  Fredric March, Mary Brian
- 584. "Martin Luther" (Box 8)
- 585. "Mary of Scotland"1936, 3 (Box 8)
  Katharine Hepburn, Fredric March
- 586. "Mary Poppins" (Box 8)
  Julie Andrews, Dick Van Dyke, Karen Dotrice, Matthew Garber
- 587. "Massacre", 2 (Box 8)
  Richard Barthelmess
- 588. "Mayerling"1968 (Box 8)
  Ava Gardner, James Mason
- 589. "Me and the Colonel" (Box 8)
  Danny Kaye, Nicole Maurey
- 590. "Meet the Wife"1931, 2 (Box 8)
  Claud Allister, Laura La Planke
- 591. "Melody Inn" (Box 8)
  Dorothy Lamour, Dick Powell, Victor Moore
- 592. "Men of Sherwood Forest" (Box 8)
  Don Taylor, Reginald Beckwith
- 593. "Mexican Spitfire Sees A Ghost"1942 (Box 8)
- 594. "Michael Strogoff" (Box 8)
  Curt Jurgens, Genevieve Page
- 595. "Midnight"1939, 2 (Box 8)
  Claudette Colbert, Don Ameche
- 596. "The Mighty"1929, 2 (Box 8)
  George Bancroft, Dorothy Revier
- 597. "The Mikado", 3 (Box 8)
- 598. "The Milky Way"1935 (Box 8)
  Harold Lloyd, Adolphe Menjou
- 599. "The Miracle Man", 2 (Box 8)
  Sylvia Sidney, Chester Morris
- 600. "The Miracle Woman"1931 (Box 8)
  Barbara Stanwyck
- 601. "Mirage" (Box 8)
  Gregory Peck, Diane Baker, Walter Matthau
- 602. "Mischief" (Box 8)
  Ralph Lynn, Winifred Shotter
- 603. "Miss Fane's Baby Is Stolen"1933 (Box 8)
  Alice Brady, Baby Leroy
- 604. "Miss Pilgrim's Progress"Michael Rennie, Yolande Donlan (Box 8)
- 605. "Mission Bloody Mary" (Box 8)
  Ken Clark
- 606. "Mississippi"1935, 2 (Box 8)
  Bing Crosby, Joan Bennett
- 607. "The Missouri Traveler", 2 (Box 8)
  Brandon de Wilde, Lee Marvin
- 608. "Mister Hulot's Holiday" (Box 8)
  Jacques Tati
- 609. "The Mistress"1965 (Box 8)
- 610. "Modern Mothers"1928 (Box 8)
  Douglas Fairbanks, Jr., Helene Chadwick
- 611. "The Mongols", 4 (Box 8)
  Anita Ekberg, Jack Palance
- 612. "Monsieur Beaucaire", 4 (Box 8)
  Bob Hope, Joan Caulfield
- 613. "Monte Carlo"1930 (Box 8)
  Claud Allister, Jeannette MacDonald, Jack Cuchanan
- 614. "Moonlight Murder", 2 (Box 8)
  Leo Carrillo, Chester Morris
- 615. "The Moonraker" (Box 8)
  Sylvia Sims, George Baker
- 616. "Morgan" (Box 8)
  Vanessa Redgrave, Robert Stephens
- 617. "Mothers of Men"1910 (Box 8)
  Gloria Whitney, Frankie Bailey
- 618. "The Moving Target" (Box 8)
  Paul Newman, Lauren Bacall, Julie Harris
- 619. "Mrs. Wiggs of the Cabbage Patch"1934 (Box 8)
  Pauline Lord, W.C. Fields, ZaSu Pitts
- 620. "Mourning Becomes Electra" (Box 8)
  Rosalind Russell, Michael Redgrave, Kirk Douglas
- 621. "Murder in the Blue Room", 4 (Box 8)
  Grace McDonald, Donald Cook
- 622. "Muder She Said" (Box 8)
  Margaret Rutherford, Arthur Kennedy
- 623. "Murders in the Rue Morgue" (Box 8)
- 624. "My American Wife"1936, 2 (Box 8)
  Francis Lederer, Ann Sothern
- 625. "My Boy"1922 (Box 8)
  Jackie Coogan
- 626. "My Little Chickadee" (Box 8)
  W.C. Fields, Mae West
- 627. "My Man Godfrey"1937 (Box 8)
  William Powell
- 628. "My Man Godfrey"1957, 45 (Box 8)
  David Niven, June Allyson
- 629. "My Wife's Family" (Box 8)
  Ronald Shiner, Ted Ray
- 630. "The Mysterious Island" (Box 8)
- 631. "Naked Alibi", 2 (Box 8)
  Sterling Hayden, Gloria Grahame
- 632. "Naked and the Dead"1958 (Box 8)
  Aldo Ray
- 633. "The Naked Edge" (Box 8)
  Gary Cooper, Deborah Kerr
- 634. "Name the Woman"1928 (Box 8)
  Huntly Gordon, Anita Stewart
- 635. "Nancy Steele Is Missing"1937 (Box 8)
  Victor McLaglen
- 636. "Never Let Go" (Box 8)
  Richard Todd, Peter Sellers
- 637. "Never Say Goodbye", 3 (Box 8)
  Rock Hudson, Cornell Borchers
- 638. "Never Too Late", 3 (Box 8)
  Richard Talmadge
- 639. "New Mexico" (Box 8)
  Lew Ayres, Marilyn Maxwell
- 640. "Niagara" (Box 8)
  Marilyn Monroe, Joseph Cotton
- 641. "The Night of the Generals" (Box 8)
  Peter O'Toole, Omar Sharif
- 642. "Night Must Fall" (Box 8)
  Albert Finney, Mona Washbourne
- 643. "Night In Paradise"1945, 42 (Box 8)
  Thomas Gomez, Merle Oberon
- 644. "Nightmare"1956 (Box 8)
- 645. "Nightmare" (Box 8)
  David Knight, Moira Redmond
- 646. "Nights of Temptation" (Box 8)
  Belinda Lee, Jacques Sernas
- 647. "Nine Hours to Rama" (Box 8)
  Horst Buchholz, Jose Ferrer
- 648. "No Highway" (Box 8)
  James Stewart, Marlene Dietrich
- 649. "No, My Darling Daughter" (Box 8)
  Michael Redgrave, Juliet Mills
- 650. "No Parking", 2 (Box 8)
  Gordon Harker, Irene Ware
- 651. "No Time To Die" (Box 8)
  Victor Mature, Leo Genn
- 652. "No Time For Flowers" (Box 8)
  Viveca Lindfors, Paul Christian
- 653. "Noah's Ark"1929, 2 (Box 8)
  (see "The Bible")
- 654. "Nobody Runs Forever" (Box 8)
  Rod Taylor, Christopher Plummer
- 655. "None But The Lonely Heart"1944 (Box 8)
  Ethel Barrymore, Cary Grant
- 656. "North to Alaska" (Box 8)
  John Wayne, Stewart Granger
- 657. "North Star" (Box 8)
  Ann Baxter, Dana Andrews, Walter Huston
- 658. "North West Frontier", 3 (Box 8)
  Kenneth More, Lauren Bacall
- 659. "Now and Forever"1934 (Box 8)
  Gary Cooper, Carole Lombard, Shirley Temple
- 660. "Number 17"1921 (Box 8)
  Harold Thomas
- 661. "Nurse Marjorie"1920 (Box 8)
  Mary Miles Minter
- 662. "O.S.S." (Box 9)
  Alan Ladd, Geraldine Fitzgerald
- 663. "Oil and Romance"1924 (Box 9)
  Gordon Clifford, Charlotte Pierce
- 664. "Old Clothes"1925, 4 (Box 9)
  Joan Crawford, Jackie Coogan
- 665. "Old Hutch"1936, 3 (Box 9)
  Wallace Beery, Eric Linden
- 666. "Old Ironsides"1926 (Box 9)
- 667. "Old Soak"1937 (Box 9)
  Wallace Beery
- 668. "Olivia" (Box 9)
  Edwige Feuillers, Marie Claire
- 669. "On The Avenue" (Box 9)
  Dick Powell, Madeleine Carroll
- 670. "On The Beach" (Box 9)
  Gregory Peck, Ava Gardner, Anthony Perkins
- 671. "On The Fiddle", 18 (Box 9)
  Alfred Lynch
- 672. "Once More, With Feeling!" (Box 9)
  Yul Brynner, Kay Kendall
- 673. "Once Upon A Honeymoon"1942 (Box 9)
  Cary Grant, Ginger Rogers
- 674. "One Desire", 2 (Box 9)
  Rock Hudson, Anne Baxter
- 675. "100 Men and a Girl", 8 (Box 9)
  Deanna Durbin, Mischa Auer
- 676. "One More Spring"1935 (Box 9)
  Janet Gaynor, Grant Mitchell
- 677. "One Night in the Tropics" (Box 9)
  Abbott & Costello, Allan
- 678. "The One That Got Away", 3 (Box 9)
  Hardy Kruger
- 679. "One, Two, Three" (Box 9)
  James Cagney, Horst Buchholz
- 680. "The Only House In London" (Box 9)
  David Hemmings, Joanna
- 681. "Only Saps Work", 2 (Box 9)
- 682. "Only Two Can Play", 5 (Box 9)
  Peter Sellers, Mai Zetterling
- 683. "Open City", 6 (Box 9)
- 684. "Oscar Wilde", 3 (Box 9)
  Robert Morley, Ralph Richardson
- 685. "Out West With The Hardys" (Box 9)
  Cecilia Parker, Mickey
- 686. "Outside the Law", 9 (Box 9)
  Ray Danton, Leigh Snowden
- 687. "The Outsider" (Box 9)
  Tony Curtis
- 688. "The Pace That Thrills"1925, 2 (Box 9)
  Mary Astor, Ben Lyon
- 689. "A Pair of Briefs" (Box 9)
  Michael Craig, Mary Peach
- 690. "Pandora and the Flying Dutchman" (Box 9)
  James Mason, Ava
- 691. "Papa Loves Mama"1931 (Box 9)
  Claude Allister, Slim Summerville
- 692. "Pardners"1933 (Box 9)
  Jackie Cooper
- 693. "Paris Bound" (Box 9)
  Leslie Fenton, Ann Harding
- 694. "Paris Palace Hotel", 2 (Box 9)
  Charles Boyer, Francoise Arnoul
- 695. "Parisian Gaieties" (Box 9)
- 696. "Parnell"1937, 2 (Box 9)
  Clark Gable, Myrna Loy
- 697. "El Paso", 3) (Box 9)
  John Payne, Gail Russell, Gabby Hayes
- 698. "Passion"1954 (Box 9)
  Cornel Wilde, Yvonne de Carlo
- 699. "Passport to Destiny"1944, 3 (Box 9)
  Walter Slezak
- 700. "Patrick the Great"1943, 4) (Box 9)
  Donald O'Connor, Peggy Ryan
- 701. "The Pawnbroker" (Box 9)
  Jaime Sanchez
- 702. "Peggy" (Box 9)
  James Best, Diana Lynn
- 703. "Peter Ibbetson"1935 (Box 9)
  Gary Cooper, Ann Harding
- 704. "Petticoat Fever" (Box 9)
  Myrna Loy, Robert Montgomery
- 705. "Phantom Lady"1943, 11 (Box 9)
  Franchot Tone, Ella Raines
- 706. "The Phantom of the Opera" (Box 9)
  Herbert Lom, Heather Sears
- 707. "The Phantom Rider"1936, 5 (Box 9)
  Buck Jones, Marla Shelton
- 708. "Pigskin Parade"1936 (Box 9)
  Betty Grable, Johnny Downs, Judy
- 709. "Pillow Talk" (Box 9)
  Rock Hudson, Doris Day, Tony Randall
- 710. "Pittsburgh" 1942 (Box 9)
  Randolph Scott, John Wayne
- 711. "The Plainsman"1936, 2 (Box 9)
  Gary Cooper, Jean Arthur
- 712. "Play It Cool" (Box 9)
  Billy Fury, Michael Anderson, Jr.
- 713. "Plunder", 2 (Box 9)
- 714. "Poppy"1936 (Box 9)
  W.C. Fields
- 715. "Portrait of a Rebel"1936 (Box 9)
  Katharine Hepburn, Herbert
- 716. "Postman's Knock", 3 (Box 9)
  Spike Milligan, Barbara Shelley
- 717. "Prehistoric Women" (Box 9)
  Laurette Luez, Allan Nixon
- 718. "The Price of Fear" (Box 9)
  Merle Oberon, Lex Barker
- 719. "Prince of Players" (Box 9)
  John Derek, Elizabeth Sellars
- 720. "The Prince Who Was A Thief" (Box 9)
  Tony Curtis, Piper Laurie
- 721. "Princess of the Nile", 7 (Box 9)
  Jeffrey Hunter, Debra Paget
- 722. "The Prisoner of Shark Island"1936 (Box 9)
  John Carradine, Warner
- 723. "The Prisoner of Zenda" (Box 9)
  Ramon Navarro, Lewis Stone,
- 724. "The Prisoner of Zenda"1936 (Box 9)
  Ronald Colman, Madeleine
- 725. "The Prisoner of Zenda" (Box 9)
  Stewart Granger, Deborah Kerr,
- 726. "Prisoners"1929 (Box 9)
  Corinne Griffith, Otto Matiesen
- 727. "The Private Life of Don Juan"1934 (Box 9)
- 728. "The Private Life of Henry VIII" (Box 9)
  Charles Laughton
- 729. "Private Number" (Box 9)
  Loretta Young, Robert Taylor, Basil
- 730. "Private's Progress" (Box 9)
  Richard Attenborough, Dennis Price
- 731. "The Professionals" (Box 9)
  Burt Lancaster, Lee Marvin, Jack Palance, Ralph Bellamy